Bright lights. Hit songs. Country's biggest star. He'd trade it
all to find the kind of love he'd only sung about.
Pure Country is a drama, music, romance film directed by Christopher Cain.
Dusty Chandler is a super star in the country music world, but
his shows have the style of a '70s rock concert.
One day he takes a walk - out of his overdone
concerts to find his real country roots.
He's helped and hindered by friends and staff, but pushes on in his
search for a real music style as well as a real romance.
Dusty Wyatt Chandler, played by George Strait.
Lula Rogers, played by Lesley Ann Warren.
Harley Tucker, played by Isabel Glasser.
Buddy Jackson, played by Kyle Chandler.
Earl Blackstock, played by John Doe.
Ernest Tucker, played by Rory Calhoun.
Pure Country is a 1992 American drama musical western film.
It was directed by Christopher Cain and stars country music singer George Strait in his
acting debut, with Lesley Ann Warren, Isabel Glasser and Kyle Chandler.
The film, while profitable with box office receipts of over $15 million against a $10 million budget, had a critical
reception generally for its storyline, although some critics spoke favorably of Strait's acting performance.
The movie's corresponding soundtrack, recorded entirely by Strait, was a commercial success as well, certifying six
times platinum by the Recording Industry Association of America and charting three singles for Strait.
The movie's success led to its expansion into the titular film series, including two
sequels as well as a stage musical of the film which debuted in 2017.
The tone is emotional.